export const jsQuiz = {
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Disney's Animal Kingdom theme park opened in Florida in which year?",
        choices: [
          "1996",
          "1994",
          "1998",
          "2000",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "1998",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the family in Mary Poppins?",
        choices: [
          "Stevens",
          "Cardson",
          "Smith",
          "Banks",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Banks",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Disney opened its first European park close to which city in 1992?",
        choices: ["Berlin", "Paris", "London", "Barcelona"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Paris",
      },
      {
        question: "In The Princess and the Frog, what is the name of the trumpet-playing alligator?",
        choices: ["Louis", "Jamie", "Jared", "Tuck"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Louis",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Disney character is a charismatic and mischievous pirate fox in Zootopia?",
        choices: [
          "Walt Strop",
          "James Tuter",
          "Brad North",
          "Nick Wilde",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Nick Wilde",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of Donald Duck's sister?",
        choices: [
          "Della",
          "Tela",
          "Bonnie",
          "Nikki",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Della",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the title of the Disney film about a young girl who enters a magical world through a secret door?",
        choices: [
          "Caroline",
          "Chronicles of Narnia",
          "Coraline",
          "Finding Nemo",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Coraline",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In Moana, what is the name of the demigod who accompanies Moana on her journey?",
        choices: ["Tefeti", "Maui", "Pui", "Cluckles"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Maui",
      },
      {
        question: "In Beauty and the Beast, what song does Belle sing about her provincial life?",
        choices: ["Gaston", "There Must Be More", "Belle", "Bonjour"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Belle",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Disney villain has a magic mirror and a desire to be the fairest of them all?",
        choices: [
          "Ursula",
          "The Wicked Witch",
          "The Evil Queen",
          "Cruella de Vil",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "The Evil Queen",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who is the wicked stepmother in Cinderella who prevents her from attending the royal ball?",
        choices: [
          "Mrs. Facilier",
          "Lady Tremaine",
          "Lady Beatrice",
          "Miss Janice",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Lady Tremaine",
      },
      {
        question: "In Hercules, who is the villainous god of the underworld?",
        choices: [
          "Zeus",
          "Hephaestus",
          "Dionysus",
          "Hades",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Hades",
      },
      {
        question:
          " What was the first roller-coaster-style attraction in Disney World?",
        choices: ["Space Mountain", "Matterhorn", "The Barnstormer", "Big Thunder Mountain"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Matterhorn",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Disney park is known for its elaborate parades and shows, including the Festival of Fantasy Parade?",
        choices: ["Disneyland Forever", "Disneyland Paris", "Tokyo Disneyland", "Magic Kingdom"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Disneyland Paris",
      },
      {
        question: "Which Disney movie features a group of singing and dancing penguins?",
        choices: [
          "Madagascar",
          "Mary Poppins",
          "Happy Feet",
          "Surf's Up",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Mary Poppins",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In Lady and the Tramp, what type of dog is Lady?",
        choices: [
          "Schnauzer",
          "Cocker Spaniel",
          "Jack Russel Terrier",
          "Mutt",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Cocker Spaniel",
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the adventurous chameleon in the movie Tangled?",
        choices: [
          "Pascal",
          "Trident",
          "Frankie",
          "Ravioli",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Pascal",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the horse in Tangled who helps Rapunzel and Flynn Rider on their journey?",
        choices: ["Maximus", "Flynn", "Stev", "Pongo"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Maximus",
      },
      {
        question: "In which year was the first full-length animated feature film released by Disney?",
        choices: ["1929", "1936", "1937", "1932"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "1937",
      },
      {
        question: "Who was the original voice of Mickey Mouse?",
        choices: [
          "Lorne Michaels",
          "Mel Blanc",
          "Walt Disney",
          "Peter Pan",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Walt Disney",
      },
    ],
  };

  export const resultInitialState = {
    score: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0,
    wrongAnswers: 0,
  };